<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PackBagBuddy</string>
    <string name="already_a_member">Already a Member?</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="skip_for_now">Skip for now</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="join_packbagbuddy">Join PackBagBuddy</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="signup">SIGNUP</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP>>></string>
    <string name="horizontal_line"><hr></hr></string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account</string>
    <string name="create_one">Create One</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="explore_india">Explore India</string>
    <string name="create_tour">Create Tour</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="nav_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="adventure_trip">Adventure Trip</string>
    <string name="view_more">View More</string>
    <string name="popular_sports">Popular Sports</string>
    <string name="flat_discount">Flat Discount</string>
    <string name="zip_lining">Zip Lining</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="facebook_com">facebook.com</string>
    <string name="find_us">Find Us</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="instagram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="youtube">Youtube</string>
    <string name="photos">Photos</string>
    <string name="campfire">Campfire</string>
    <string name="view_details">view details</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="web">Web</string>
    <string name="comp">Comp</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="company_name">Company Name</string>
    <string name="company_description">Company Description</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="reason">Reason</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="order">Order</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="at_packbagbuddy_we_re_all_about_ensuring_you_get_the_best_experience_you_can_through_your_tours">At PackBagBuddy, we’re all about ensuring you get the best experience you can through your tours.</string>
    <string name="privacy1">
        This privacy policy is for www.packbagbuddy.com and served by PackBagBuddy Travel Agency LLP and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.
\n \n
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations &amp; requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
\n \n
<b>The Website</b>
        \n
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website comply’s to all India’s national laws and requirements for user privacy.
\n \n
<b>Use of Cookies</b>
        \n
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer / device.
\n \n
Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.
\n \n
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google’s privacy policy here for further information [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html ].
\n \n
Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.
\n \n
<b>Email Newsletter</b>
        \n
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text / banner / image links to other websites.)
\n \n
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
\n \n
<b>External Links</b>
        \n
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text / banner / image links to other websites.)
\n \n
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
\n \n
<b>Adverts and Sponsored Links</b>
        \n
This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.
\n \n
Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertisers website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computers hard drive. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
\n \n
<b>Social Media Platforms</b>
        \n
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.
\n \n
Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate/engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.
\n \n
This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
\n \n
<b>Shortened Links in Social Media</b>
        \n
This website and its owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages. By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy urls [web addresses]
\n \n
Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened urls published on social media platforms by this website and its owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine urls are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.
\n \n
    </string>

    <string name="cancellationright1">
        This Cancellation and Refunds policy is for www.packbagbuddy.com and served by PackBagBuddy Travel Agency LLP and governs the users who choose to use it.
\n \n
Cancellation and Refunds policies vary with different experiences/tours/trips and are displayed for the particular experience/tour/trip in the details of the particular experience/tour/trip.
\n \n
Once the refund is approved, the concerned refund amount will be processed within 14 days of approval.
\n \n
        The refund will be initiated manually by PackBagBuddy executives on approval.
\n \n
Neither PackBagBuddy nor the Operators selling their tours on packbagbuddy.com offer or pay any discounts or refunds for missed or unused services which were missed or unused by the traveller due to no fault of PackBagBuddy, or operators working with PackBagBuddy, which shall include any termination of the traveller’s participation in the tour due to the traveller’s own fault, negligence or breach of these Terms.
\n \n
Certain Tours may be weather-dependent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event of inclement weather, the Operator has the discretion as to whether the weather conditions will prevent the Tour from taking place. As an Operator, if you need to cancel an Group Tour for reasons of inclement weather, you must contact the Traveller and PackBagBuddy (at admin@packbagbuddy.com as early as possible. Subject to the Traveller’s consent, the Operator and the Traveller may choose to reschedule the Group Tour for another date. If the Group Tour cannot be rescheduled, as a Traveller, please contact PackBagBuddy so we may assist in finding a replacement, non-weather-dependent Group Tour. For clarity, in the event the alternative Group Tour is of a higher price than the former, you may be responsible for any difference in price. In the event the alternative Group Tour is of a lower price, you may be entitled to a partial refund for the difference. As a Traveller, if you have contacted PackBagBuddy as provided above and PackBagBuddy is unable to find you a replacement Group Tour, PackBagBuddy may refund the Payment for such booking to the Traveller within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation.
\n \n
All disputes arising will be interpreted in accordance with the laws of Ahmedabad, Gujarat Jurisdiction, without regard to its conflict-of-law provisions. You and we agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of a state court located in Ahmedabad, Gujarat.
\n \n
    </string>

    <string name="copyright1">
                PackBagBuddy is a marketplace where mostly local suppliers / vendors upload the content and we have developed our in-house rules in order to prevent any misalignment of interests between the former and the later. Thereby also attempting to ensure that no material which is inconsistent with our terms and conditions set forth herein is present on the website, or in any physical form with the branding of PackBagBuddy.
\n \n
A visitor to the website may not reproduce, perform, create derivative works from, republish or upload in any way whatsoever any content from the website without the prior written consent of the company. You may, however, download any downloadable items displayed on the website, for personal, non-commercial home use only, provided all copyright and other notices contained in the contents are left intact.
\n \n
Herein any mention of PackBagBuddy, us or the company is a direct reference to the company PackBagBuddy Travel Agency LLP. Also any mention of content will include content in any form including in the form of media based content such as images, videos and presentation slides.
\n \n
<b>For Local Guides/Vendors/Tour Suppliers/PackBagBuddy agents/Partners:</b>
                \n
Upload only 100% unique content. The content should not be copied from any other website or any digital or physical source of information. If you have same the itinerary on your own website(in cases where required, you will have to provide substantial proof* of being the owner) we would suggest that you rewrite the content which will be different in structure but the same as the meaning you are trying to derive. In such a case, we may be able to assist you with content writers to undergo the task of rewriting the content.
\n \n
                The experience/tour/trip needs to be conducted by you and not by any other party. You should have full rights of the any information displayed on PackBagBuddy website by you. The experience/tour/trip cannot be outsourced by you to any other third party. Hence by uploading an experience/tour/trip onto our website, you agree to being the party which conducts the experience/tour/trip in it’s entirety**.
\n \n
                The uploader must own full rights to any media uploaded by him/her. All media including videos/pictures/slides/marketing material etc need to be owned by you/your company and PackBagBuddy holds the right to use it there onwards without the requirement for attribution of credits.
\n \n
                As per Rule 3, you should have sole and entire copyright for any form of information*** uploaded by you. Please do not upload anything which does not belong to you or your company and for which you do not have sole ownership. We prohibit you to use anything under Creative Commons licence. If any violation of this rule takes place, indicated to us by either the company officials or the general public or the owner of the material itself, the infringing experience/tour/trip will be immediately removed from the website and you will be held responsible for any kind of infringement be it image/video/content or anything else. This will also result in the removal of all experiences/tours/trips uploaded by you onto our website and will end in a permanent ban from being a supplier for PackBagBuddy.
\n \n
                Mismatch in the media and content uploaded is a bannable offense. If the images of the experience/tour/trip and the content describing it do not match or are seen to be intentionally depicting incorrect information in order to misinform the viewer of the content, the experience/tour/trip will be removed and the supplier will be banned.

         \n  \n In case of any true claims the company will pass on your details to the copyright claimer. This is subjected to PackBagBuddy’s decision on that matter after it’s analysis on that issue.
\n \n
                If a supplier reports any copyright violation, appropriate actions will be taken within three business days.
\n \n
                By submitting listing on the website, you are consenting to its display in the marketplace, and/or on any of the other company websites. You are also consenting to its use for promotional purposes by the company.
\n \n
                Also please note that the textual content uploaded by you on the PackBagBuddy website should not be loaded/copied anywhere on any other website for 6 months after the tour is active on the website. We do not restrict you to use any other marketplace or website but the content should not be duplicated on other websites for at least 6 months.
\n \n
                By uploading or providing details of any tour/activity conducted by you/your company you take the entire responsibility of any copyright infringement issues pertaining to that tour/activity. We do a few random checks at our end but the final responsibility will be yours on all the materials provided.
\n \n
<b>For Copyright Claimants:</b>
                \n
                In case of any copyright infringement, please send us an email detailing as to which experience/tour/trip is in violation of copyrights and specifically what content on that page violates the copyright. Along with this, it is required that you submit proof of your copyright claim which should include proof which shows you to be the owner of the violating material.
\n \n
                In case of any reported copyright infringement, the copyright claim including all the related details will be sent to the vendor. Our team will then do a follow up with the vendor on this which may take upto seven business days and may be extended to fourteen days. If the vendor does not reply within this time period, it will be assumed that the claimant’s claim is valid and on the seventh day, the experience/tour/trip will be removed from our website. In case the vendor’s reply is inconclusive and he/she is unable to provide proper proof as to his/her ownership of the material under question, it will be deemed to be a violation of copyright laws and the entire experience/tour/trip including the infringing material will be removed and the vendor will be banned from PackBagBuddy. After this, the claimant will be connected with the vendor to take the legal issue forward.
\n \n
                To enable us to address your concerns, please provide the following information:
\n \n
                For each allegedly infringing image or piece of content that you wish to have removed from our website, provide the exact permanent URL for the page containing the material and details of which is the infringing piece of content.
\n \n
                Provide information which is reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact you: an email address is preferred, as well as a telephone contact number.
\n \n
                Provide the following information detailing your claim to ownership of the copyright in the allegedly infringing material:
\n \n
                Proof of copyright in the image or text concerned, namely proof of registration of the image under the DMCA or absent such registration,
\n \n
                A detailed description of where the photograph was taken, by whom, who or what the subject of the image is, and
\n \n
                Evidence to support your claim that you own the copyright in the image.
\n \n
                We will not comply with requests to remove an image where the complainant cannot prove that they own the copyright in the image in question.
\n \n
                All claims will be taken seriously by the company and any intentionally false claims**** and/or misrepresentation of facts in a claim will result in the company proceeding to take legal action against the claimant which will include liability for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees).
\n \n
                Any content submitted becomes the property of PackBagBuddy to do with as we wish.
\n \n
<b>Images Terms of Use:</b>
                \n
The following types of images cannot be uploaded on the website:
\n \n
                A work that uses free or purchased components from any other source unless you have an express license to do so.
\n \n
                A work that uses in whole or in part government or military property.
\n \n
                A work that includes a photograph or image of a private location unless you have express permission to do so, which you can produce on demand.
\n \n
                A work that includes a person or recognizable human feature unless you have express permission to do so, which you can produce on demand.
\n \n
                The only images allowed are those that are:
\n
                created by the author;
\n
                purchased or acquired under an appropriate license that allows use in an item for sale.
\n
                Please note:
\n
                PackBagBuddy is a marketplaces for tours and activities and does not take any responsibility for any of the content uploaded on our website in the tours, activities and experiences sections, including certain guest posts on the blog. The uploader is solely responsible for the content which he/she has uploaded. As a precaution, in most cases we will take confirmation from the supplier that the content provided is original and that the supplier is it’s sole owner.
                \n
                PackBagBuddy holds the right to delete any content from the website at anytime and the company’s decision will be the final one.
\n
                The content provided will be watermarked to avoid any piracy issues.
\n
                Since the company is registered in Ahmedabad, legal issues, including issues pertaining to copyright violations, will be subject to the jurisdiction of Ahmedabad (Gujarat).
\n

               \n  * The appropriate amount of proof considered to be substantial will be decided by the company.
\n \n

                ** This may be subject to the certain leniencies in the case of unforeseeable circumstances and if the company has been informed with a substantial prior notice that the operator will be using a third party without which the experience/tour/trip will not be able to proceed.
\n \n
                *** Information here can be in any form including media, videos, pictures, content etc.
\n \n
                **** Here intentionally false claims will be defined by the company as those which are meant to mislead the company or claims which are made in order to misuse the company’s resources. The company can be contacted to provide more information regarding what falls under this category.
\n \n

        </string>

    <string name="legal1"><i>Policies</i> means a course or principle of action adopted or proposed by an organization or individual.
Policies are generally adopted by a governance body within an organization.
   \n \n\n    Below are the policies that govern PackBagBuddy and its users –
\n
    </string>
    <string name="legal2">
        <u>Terms and Conditions</u>
    </string>
    <string name="legal3">
        <u>Copyright Policy</u></string>
    <string name="legal4"><u>Privacy Policy</u></string>
    <string name="legal5">
<u>Cancellations and Refunds
    </u>
    </string>

    <string name="tnc1">PackBagBuddy (hereafter referred to as “PackBagBuddy”,”we”, “us”, or “our”) provides an online platform that connects Operators who have knowledge and experience with a particular travel destination or activity with Travellers seeking to experience such destinations and activities (collectively with the Site and Application (each as defined below), the “Services”).
\n \n
The Services are accessible at packbagbuddy.com and any other websites through which PackBagBuddy makes the Services available (collectively, the “Site”) and any related applications (the “Application”). By using the Services, you agree to comply with and be legally bound by the terms and conditions of these Terms of Service (“Terms”), whether or not you become a registered user of the Services. These Terms govern your access to and use of the Site, Application and Services and all Collective Content (defined below) and constitute a binding legal agreement between you and PackBagBuddy.
\n \n
Please carefully read these Terms and our Privacy Policy and our Legal Notice, each of which is incorporated by reference into these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, you have no right to obtain information from or otherwise continue using the Services. Failure to use the Services in accordance with these Terms may subject you to civil and criminal penalties.
\n \n
THE SERVICES COMPRISE AN ONLINE PLATFORM THROUGH WHICH OPERATORS (DEFINED BELOW) MAY CREATE LISTINGS (DEFINED BELOW) FOR GROUP TOURS (DEFINED BELOW) AND TRAVELLERS (DEFINED BELOW) MAY LEARN ABOUT AND BOOK SUCH GROUP TOURS.
\n \n
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT PackBagBuddy IS NOT A PARTY TO ANY AGREEMENTS ENTERED INTO BETWEEN OPERATORS AND TRAVELLERS, NOR IS PackBagBuddy AN AGENT OR INSURER. PackBagBuddy HAS NO CONTROL OVER THE CONDUCT OF OPERATORS, TRAVELLERS AND OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICES OR ANY GROUP TOURS, AND DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY IN THIS REGARD.
\n \n
        <b>Key Terms</b>
       \n
“Collective Content” means Member Content and PackBagBuddy Content. “Content” means text, graphics, images, music, software (excluding the Application), audio, video, information or other materials. “Operator Service provider or Vendor” means a Member who creates a Listing via the Services. “Listing” means an Activity or Tour that is listed by an Operator as available for booking via the Services. “Member” means a person who completes PackBagBuddy’s account registration process, including, but not limited to Operators and Travellers, as described under “Account Registration” below. “Member Content” means all Content that a Member posts, uploads, publishes, submits or transmits to be made available through the Services.
\n \n
“Tax” or “Taxes” mean Goods and Services taxes (GST). “PackBagBuddy Content” means all Content that PackBagBuddy makes available through the Services, including any Content licensed from a third party, but excluding Member Content. “Traveller” means a Member who requests a booking of a Group Tour via the Services, or a Member who participates in an Group Tour and is not the Operator for such Tour. Certain portions of the Services (and your access to or use of certain aspects of the Services or Collective Content) may have different terms and conditions posted or may require you to agree with and accept additional terms and conditions. If there is a conflict between these Terms and terms and conditions posted for a specific portion of the Services, or Collective Content, the latter terms and conditions will take precedence with respect to your use of or access to that portion of the Services, or Collective Content.
\n \n
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICES OR BY DOWNLOADING OR POSTING ANY CONTENT FROM OR ON THE SITE, VIA THE APPLICATION OR OTHERWISE THROUGH THE SERVICES YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, AND THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS, WHETHER OR NOT YOU HAVE REGISTERED WITH THE SERVICES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, THEN YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICES, OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT.
\n \n
If you accept or agree to these Terms on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to bind that company or other legal entity to these Terms and, in such event, “you” and “your” will refer and apply to that company or other legal entity.
\n \n
        <b>Modification</b>
        \n
PackBagBuddy reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify the Services at any time and without prior notice. If we modify these Terms, we will post the modification on the Site or via the Services or provide you with notice of the modification. We will also update the “Last Updated Date” at the top of these Terms. Any changes will become effective immediately upon your acceptance of the modified Terms, whether by, without limitation, creating a Listing or requesting the booking of an Group Tour. If the modified Terms are not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease using the Services.
\n \n
<b>Eligibility</b>
        \n
The Services can be used to facilitate the listing, reviewing, searching, comparing, meeting other people, entering contests and booking of tours and activities (“Group Tours”). Such Group Tours are included in Listings on the Services by Operators. You may view Listings as an unregistered visitor to the Services; however, if you wish to book a Tour or create a Listing, you must either register to create a PackBagBuddy Account (defined below) or provide your email address. As stated above, PackBagBuddy makes available a platform or marketplace with related technology for Travellers and Operators to meet online, write reviews, search, compare, enter contests and arrange for bookings of Group Tours.PackBagBuddy is not an operator of tours, activities or other Group Tours, nor is it a provider of group tours or activities and PackBagBuddy does not own, sell, resell, furnish, provide, manage and/or control any transportation, tour or travel services.
\n \n
For any kind of visa, inner line permits, forest department or government permissions and tickets to entrance parks which are part of your itinerary, please check with the tour operator or plan them in advance. PackBagBuddy does not provide these services or checks any of these services. PackBagBuddy only facilitates ticket booking and does not take any guarantee of any kind of permissions or tickets required in course of your tour itinerary. In case you miss and do not have required documents due to which you are not able to complete your tour, PackBagBuddy or tour operator will not be liable for the act.
\n \n
PackBagBuddy’s responsibilities are limited to:facilitating the availability of the Services andserving as the limited agent of each Operator for the purpose of accepting payments from Travellers on behalf of the Operator.
\n \n
PLEASE NOTE THAT, AS STATED ABOVE, THE SERVICES ARE INTENDED TO BE USED TO FACILITATE THE BOOKING OF GROUP TOURS. PackBagBuddy CANNOT AND DOES NOT CONTROL THE CONTENT CONTAINED IN ANY LISTINGS AND THE CONDITION, LEGALITY OR SUITABILITY OF ANY GROUP TOURS. PackBagBuddy IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR AND DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL LIABILITY RELATED TO ANY AND ALL LISTINGS AND TOURS. ACCORDINGLY, ANY BOOKINGS WILL BE MADE AT THE TRAVELER’S OWN RISK.
\n
    </string>
    <string name="tnc2">
<b>Account Registration</b>
        \n
For Operators – Tour operators that wish to take advantage of PackBagBuddy services and sell their tours on the packbagbuddy.com Global Marketplace need to first submit their application. PackBagBuddy reviews all sign up requests and assesses the compatibility of the tour operators’ product with the packbagbuddy.com Marketplace. This review process can take up to 2 weeks as the product, company, market fit, bonding, safety and global reputation of the company is assessed. Upon reviewing the sign up request the PackBagBuddy team informs the operator whether or not working together is possible. PackBagBuddy reserves the right to decline the application at this stage, or any other, stage. If the first screening is positive, the operator will be asked to fill out a application form and submit it to the PackBagBuddy team. Once this form is accepted, processed and the application is confirmed by PackBagBuddy, PackBagBuddy will guide the operator through the next sign up steps, which includes uploading tour listings, installation of tools like Facebook Applications and assists the operator wherever possible. Before PackBagBuddy can start driving bookings for the operator, the operator must agree to PackBagBuddy Terms and Conditions in writing via e-mail.
\n \n
For Travellers – In order to access certain features of the Services and to book a Tour, you can create an account (“PackBagBuddy Account”) and become a Member. You may register to join the Services directly via the Site or Application using the link at the top of any page or as otherwise described in this section. You may also be able to register to join by logging into your account with certain third party social networking sites (“SNS”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook); each such account, a “Third Party Account”, via our Site or Application, as described below. As part of the functionality of the Services, you may be able to link your PackBagBuddy Account with Third Party Accounts, by either:providing your Third Party Account login information to PackBagBuddy through the Services; orallowing PackBagBuddy to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to PackBagBuddy and/or grant PackBagBuddy access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating PackBagBuddy to pay any fees or making PackBagBuddy subject to any usage limitations imposed by such third party service providers. By granting PackBagBuddy access to any Third Party Accounts, you understand that PackBagBuddy may access, make available and store (if applicable) any Content that you have provided to and stored in your Third Party Account (“SNS Content”) so that it is available on and through the Services via your PackBagBuddy Account and PackBagBuddy Account profile page. You agree that PackBagBuddy may request your email address, access to photos; friends list to help verify your identity; share your updates and photos; and to be contacted by us. Unless otherwise specified in these Terms, all SNS Content, if any, will be considered to be Member Content for all purposes of these Terms. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, personally identifiable information that you post to your Third Party Accounts may be available on and through your PackBagBuddy Account on the Services. Please note that if a Third Party Account or associated service becomes unavailable or PackBagBuddy’s access to such Third Party Account is terminated by the third party service provider, then SNS Content may no longer be available on and through the Services. You have the ability to configure certain portions of the connection between your PackBagBuddy Account and your Third Party Accounts, at any time, by accessing the “Profile” section of the Services.
\n \n
PLEASE NOTE THAT YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH THE THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNTS IS GOVERNED SOLELY BY YOUR AGREEMENT(S) WITH SUCH THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS.
\n \n
PackBagBuddy makes no effort to review any SNS Content for any purpose, including but not limited to, for accuracy, legality or non-infringement and PackBagBuddy is not responsible for any SNS Content. We will create your PackBagBuddy Account and your PackBagBuddy Account profile page for your use of the Services based upon the personal information you provide to us or that we obtain via an SNS as described above. You may not have more than one (1) active PackBagBuddy Account. You agree to provide accurate, current and complete information during the registration process and to update such information to keep it accurate, current and complete. PackBagBuddy reserves the right to suspend or terminate your PackBagBuddy Account and your access to the Services if you create more than one (1) PackBagBuddy Account or if any information provided during the registration process or thereafter proves to be inaccurate, not current or incomplete. You are responsible for safeguarding your password. You agree that you will not disclose your password to any third party and that you will take sole responsibility for any activities or actions under your PackBagBuddy Account, whether or not you have authorized such activities or actions. You will immediately notify PackBagBuddy of any unauthorized use of your PackBagBuddy Account.packbagbuddy.com performs regular backups on all servers to ensure critical files are never lost. However PackBagBuddy is NOT responsible for lost data, time, income or any other resource due to faulty backups or non-existent backups. Please always backup your own data for Redundancy.
\n \n
<b>Tour Listings</b>
        \n
Operators may create Listings. To this end, you will be asked a variety of questions about the Tour to be listed, including, but not limited to, the location, capacity, itinerary, features, availability of the Group Tour and pricing and related rules and financial terms. Operators working with PackBagBuddy are responsible for making sure that their tour listings on the packbagbuddy.com Marketplace are up-to-date so that travellers who wish to book their tours are presented with correct information. Tour operators are responsible for updating their tour information – either manually using the PackBagBuddy Dashboard, or by supplying the PackBagBuddy team with a fully functional information over email. Listings will be made publicly available via the Services. Other Members will be able to book your Tours via the Services based upon the information provided in your Listing. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for any and all Listings you post. Accordingly, you represent and warrant that any Listing you post and the booking of, or Traveller taking of, a Tour in a Listing you postwill not breach any agreements you have entered into with any third parties (such as any agreements with or rules of employers or local tourism agencies) andwillbe in compliance with all applicable laws, Tax requirements, and rules and regulations that may apply to any Group Tour included in a Listing you post, including, but not limited to, tourism, tour guide licensing laws, and other laws governing events and tours of public spaces and other venues andnot conflict with the rights of third parties. Please note that PackBagBuddy assumes no responsibility for an Operator’s compliance with any applicable laws, rules and regulations. PackBagBuddy reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Listing for any reason, including Listings that PackBagBuddy, in its sole discretion, considers to be objectionable for any reason, in violation of these Terms or otherwise harmful to the Services. You understand and agree that PackBagBuddy does not act as an insurer or as a contracting agent for you as an Operator. If a Traveller requests a booking of your Group Tour and participates in your Group Tour, any agreement you enter into with such Traveller is between you and the Traveller and PackBagBuddy is not a party thereto.
\n \n
Not withstanding the foregoing, PackBagBuddy serves as the limited authorized agent of the operator for the purpose of accepting payments from the traveller on behalf of the Operator and is responsible for transmitting such payments to the operator, subject to these Terms. When you create a Listing, you may also choose to include certain requirements, which must be met by the Members who are eligible to request a booking of your Tour. Any member wishing to book tours included in Listings with such requirements must meet these requirements. You acknowledge and agree that, as an operator, you are responsible for your own acts and omissions and are also responsible for the acts and omissions of any individuals who are present during the group tour at your request or invitation, excluding the traveller. PackBagBuddy recommends that operators obtain appropriate insurance for their Tours. Please review any insurance policy that you may have for your tour carefully, and in particular please make sure that you are familiar with and understand any exclusions to, and any deductibles that may apply for, such insurance policy, including, but not limited to, whether or not your insurance policy will cover the actions or inactions of travellers while participating in your group tour.
\n \n
<b>No Endorsement</b>
        \n
PackBagBuddy does not endorse any Members or any Tours. In addition, although these Terms require Members to provide accurate information, we do not attempt to confirm, and do not confirm, any Member’s purported identity. You are responsible for determining the identity and suitability of others who you contact via the Services. We will not be responsible for any damage or harm resulting from your interactions with other Members. By using the Services, you agree that any legal remedy or liability that you seek to obtain for actions or omissions of other Members or other third parties will be limited to a claim against the particular Members or other third parties who caused you harm and you agree not to attempt to impose liability on, or seek any legal remedy from PackBagBuddy with respect to such actions or omissions. Accordingly, we encourage you to communicate directly with other Members via the Services regarding any bookings or Listings made by you. This limitation shall not apply to any claim by an Operator against PackBagBuddy regarding the remittance of payments received from a Traveller by PackBagBuddy on behalf of an Operator, which instead shall be subject to the limitations described in the section below entitled “Limitation of Liability”.
\n \n
<b>Bookings and Financial Terms for Operators</b>
        \n
If you are an Operator and a booking is requested for your Group Tour via the Services, you will be required to either confirm or decline the booking using PackBagBuddy’s Messaging System within the specified timeframe (which is generally within 24 hours of when the booking is requested, as determined by PackBagBuddy in its sole discretion) or the booking request will be automatically accepted. If you decide to decline a booking of an Tour within the specified timeframe, any amounts collected by PackBagBuddy for the requested booking will be refunded to the applicable Traveller’s credit card and any pre-authorization of such credit card will be released. You understand and agree that once a Traveller requests a booking of your Group Tour, the price for such booking may not be altered after you confirm the booking without first obtaining the Travellers consent. If you have not yet confirmed the Traveller’s booking you can amend the price, details, add discounts, food funds, single supplements and other local payment so long as you advise the Traveller of these changes before you confirm the booking to allow Travellers to consent to your changes.
\n \n
When a booking is requested via the Services, we may share with you the first and last name of the Traveller who has requested the booking. The Deposit amount displayed on the booking page is set by you. Where applicable, Taxes may be charged in addition to the Group Tour Cost. The Group Tour Cost and applicable Taxes are collectively referred to in these Terms as the “Total Cost”. The amounts due and payable by a Traveller solely relating to an Operator’s Group Tour are the “Tour Cost”. Please note that it is you and not PackBagBuddy which determines the Tour Cost and you agree this Cost will be exactly the same Cost stated on your website.
\n \n
If the Departure is 60 days, unless otherwise stated on the tour page, or more from the booking date, PackBagBuddy will only collect the Deposit at the time of booking confirmation (i.e. when you confirm the booking within the specified timeframe). The Balance of Payment (defined as the Group Tour Cost minus the Deposit) will be automatically collected from the Traveller by us, 60 days, unless otherwise stated on the tour page, prior to the departure date, unless otherwise stated on the tour page. PackBagBuddy is only liable to pay to the Operator the payments collected from the Traveller minus PackBagBuddy’s Service Fee. If the Traveller’s Balance of Payment transaction fails on the due date, the Operator agrees to provide the Traveller with a grace period of 5 days to pay the Balance of Payment via PackBagBuddy’s E2B. If the Balance of Payment remains unpaid prior to the departure date the Operator may choose to cancel the Traveller’s booking where the Deposit will be forfeited. Or the Operator may choose to extend the grace period as the Operator determines. If a booking is found to be fraudulent by the PackBagBuddy Team, we will notify you and you must cancel any invoice to PackBagBuddy. After you confirm a booking, you are responsible for invoicing PackBagBuddy for the original tour price listed in the packbagbuddy.com tour listing at the point of booking request (which must correspond to the pricing on your website) minus PackBagBuddy’s Service fee. PackBagBuddy’s Service fee are displayed in your PackBagBuddy Dashboard. Invoices are to be emailed to support@packbagbuddy.com. Invoices must have a payment due date of the 5th business day of the next calendar month after the tour departure date. Each tour booking must have its own invoice. PackBagBuddy will pay the Net Amount (defined as being the Group Tour Cost minus the Service Fee) to your nominated bank account. We are not responsible for delays in remitting Tour Fees, which can vary based on the bank, currency, location, etc. We are responsible for emailing the Traveller with a booking receipt for their payments. You are responsible for emailing any documentation, other necessary details and vouchers to the Traveller.
\n
        </string>
    <string name="tnc3">
<b>Appointment of PackBagBuddy as Payment Agent for Operator</b>
        \n
Each Operator hereby appoints PackBagBuddy as the Operator’s limited agent solely for the purpose of collecting payments made by Travellers on behalf of the Operator. Each Operator agrees that payment made by a Traveller to PackBagBuddy shall be considered the same as a payment made directly to the Operator and the Operator will make the Group Tour available to Traveller in the agreed upon manner as if the Operator has received the Part Payment. In accepting appointment as the limited authorized agent of the Operator, PackBagBuddy assumes no liability for any acts or omissions of the Operator. Operators acknowledge and agree that PackBagBuddy reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to introduce and collect other fees from you in accordance with the Modification Section of these Terms. Please note that PackBagBuddy will provide notice of new fees via the Services, prior to implementing such new features.
\n \n
<b>Bookings and Financial Terms for Travellers</b>
        \n
The Operators, not PackBagBuddy, are solely responsible for honouring any confirmed bookings and making available any Group Tours reserved through the Services. If you, as a Traveller, choose to enter into a transaction with an Operator for the booking of a Group Tour, you agree and understand that you will be required to enter into an agreement (including releases) with the Operator and you agree to accept any terms, conditions, rules and restrictions associated with such Tour imposed by the Operator. Operators may not change the Tour Cost after a booking has been confirmed unless the Operator asks for your Consent (changes might include additional services that you request from the Operator). If a booking has not yet been confirmed by the Operator, the Operator may change the price, details, add discounts, local payments and other services requested by you but the Operator must notify you of this change and you must consent to this change before the Operator can confirm your booking. You acknowledge and agree that you, and not PackBagBuddy, will be responsible for performing the obligations of any such agreements, that PackBagBuddy is not a party to such agreements, and that, with the exception of its payment obligations hereunder, PackBagBuddy disclaims all liability arising from or related to any such agreements. You acknowledge and agree that, notwithstanding the fact that PackBagBuddy is not a party to any agreements between you and the Operator, PackBagBuddy acts as the Operator’s payment agent for the limited purpose of accepting payments from you on behalf of the Operator. Upon your payment of amounts to PackBagBuddy which are due to the Operator, your payment obligation to the Operator is extinguished, and PackBagBuddy will remit to the Operator the difference between the Tour Cost minus the Service Fee (defined below). The secure payment provider that PackBagBuddy uses to process all payments is EBS or PayU.
\n \n
The Booking Page for a Tour will specify the Total Cost called the Tour Cost. As noted above the Operator is required to either confirm or decline the booking. If a requested booking is cancelled (i.e. not confirmed by the applicable Operator), any amounts collected by PackBagBuddy will be refunded to such Traveller, depending on the selections the Traveller makes via the Site and Application, and any pre-authorization of such Traveller’s credit card will be released, if applicable, and you acknowledge we will refund these amounts as soon as possible but the speed at which these amounts are returned to your credit card is often something you will need to discuss with our bank and is not something we are responsible for. You agree to pay PackBagBuddy for the Deposit for any booking requested in connection with your PackBagBuddy Account if such requested bookings are confirmed by the applicable Operator if the departure date is greater than 60 days, unless otherwise stated on the tour page, to the booking date. If the departure date is within 60 days, unless otherwise stated on the tour page, of the booking date the Tour Cost is payable. If you have paid a Deposit then the Balance of Payment will be automatically deducted from the credit card stored in your Account Profile 60 days, unless otherwise stated on the tour page, prior to the departure date. If your Balance of Payment fails on the due date (60 days prior to the departure date, unless otherwise stated on the tour page) you have a grace period of 5 days to pay the Balance of Payment. If the Balance of Payment remains unpaid on the 55th day prior to the departure date the Operator may choose to cancel your booking and your Deposit will be forfeited. Or the Operator may choose to extend the grace period at their sole discretion and the Operator has no obligation to provide an extension. In order to establish a booking pending the applicable Operator’s confirmation of your requested booking, you understand and agree that PackBagBuddy, on behalf of the Operator, reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to (i) obtain a pre-authorization via your credit card for the Part Payment and/or (ii) charge your credit card a nominal amount, not to exceed one dollar ($1), or a similar sum in the currency in which you are transacting (e.g. one euro or one British pound) to verify your credit card. Once the Operators confirms your booking, PackBagBuddy will collect the payment in accordance with the terms and conditions of these Terms and the pricing terms set forth in the applicable Listing. Please note that PackBagBuddy cannot control any fees that may be charged to you by your bank related to PackBagBuddy’s collection of payments, and PackBagBuddy disclaims all liability in this regard. In connection with your requested booking, you will be asked to provide customary billing information such as name, billing address and credit card information either to PackBagBuddy or its third party payment processor. You agree to pay PackBagBuddy for any confirmed bookings made in connection with your PackBagBuddy Account in accordance with these Terms by one of the methods as may be described on the Site or Application – e.g. by credit card. You hereby authorize the collection of such amounts by charging the credit card provided as part of requesting the booking, either directly by PackBagBuddy or indirectly, via a third party online payment processor or by one of the other payment methods as may be described on the Site or Application. If you are directed to PackBagBuddy’s third party payment processor, you may be subject to terms and conditions governing use of that third party’s service and that third party’s personal information collection practices. Please review such terms and conditions and privacy policy before using the services. Once your confirmed booking transaction is complete you will receive a confirmation email summarizing your confirmed booking and the Operator will email documentation and vouchers to your email address.
\n \n
<b>Service Fees only apply to Operators</b>
        \n
In consideration for providing the Services, PackBagBuddy collects a service fee only from Operators (“Service Fees”). A Service Fee is made up of the based upon a percentage of the amount of the Group Tour Cost which is defined in the Operator’s PackBagBuddy T n C. Where applicable, Taxes may also be charged in addition to the Service Fee. Services Fees are deducted from the Group Tour Cost before remitting the balance to the Operator (please note that we will not be responsible for delays in remitting Group Tour Fees, which can vary based on the bank, currency, location, etc). Balances will be remitted by PackBagBuddy to Operators via cheque, direct deposit or other payment methods described on the Site or via the Application, in the Operator’s currency of choice, depending upon the selections the Operator makes via the Services. Please note that for any payments by PackBagBuddy, we will pay our bank’s costs and and you are responsible to pay your bank’s costs. More information on Service Fees can be found in your Dashboard by going to Profile > PackBagBuddy Package. Except as otherwise provided herein, Service Fees are non-refundable.
\n \n
<b>Cancellation and Refunds</b>
        \n
View our Cancellation and Refunds Policy.
\n \n
<b>Taxes</b>
        \n
You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for determining your applicable Tax reporting requirements in consultation with your tax advisors. PackBagBuddy cannot and does not offer Tax-related advice to any Members of the Services. Additionally, please note that each Operator is responsible for determining local indirect Taxes and for including any applicable Taxes to be collected or obligations relating to applicable Taxes in Listings.
\n \n
<b>Member Conduct</b>
        \n
You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for compliance with any and all laws, rules, regulations, and Tax obligations that may apply to your use of the Site, Application, Services and Content. In connection with your use of the Services, you may not and you agree that you will not: violate any local, state, provincial, national, or other law or regulation, or any order of a court, including, without limitation, zoning restrictions and Tax regulations; use manual or automated software, devices, scripts robots, other means or processes to access, “scrape,” “crawl” or “spider” any web pages or other services contained in the Site, Application, Services or Content; use the Services for any commercial or other purposes that are not expressly permitted by these Terms; copy, store or otherwise access any information contained on the Services or Content for purposes not expressly permitted by these Terms; infringe the rights of any person or entity, including without limitation, their intellectual property, privacy, publicity or contractual rights; interfere with or damage the Services, including, without limitation, through the use of viruses, cancel bots, Trojan horses, harmful code, flood pings, Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks, packet or IP spoofing, forged routing or electronic mail address information or similar methods or technology; use the Services to transmit, distribute, post or submit any information concerning any other person or entity, including without limitation, photographs of others without their permission, personal contact information or credit, debit, calling card or account numbers; use the Services in connection with the distribution of unsolicited commercial email (“spam”) or advertisements unrelated to Group Tours; “stalk” or harass any other user of the Services or collect or store any personally identifiable information about any other user other than for purposes of transacting as a PackBagBuddy Traveller or Operator; offer, as an Operator, any Group Tours that you do not yourself have permission to provide (without limiting the foregoing, you will not list Group Tours as an Operator if you are serving in the capacity of an agent for a third party); offer, as an Operator, any Group Tour that may not be provided pursuant to the terms and conditions of an agreement with a third party; register for more than one PackBagBuddy Account or register for a PackBagBuddy Account on behalf of an individual other than yourself; contact an Operator for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking, such Operator’s Group Tours or Listings; contact a Traveller for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking or such Traveller’s use of the Services; when acting as a Traveller or otherwise, recruit or otherwise solicit any Operator or other Member to join third party services or websites that are competitive to PackBagBuddy, without PackBagBuddy’s prior written approval (for clarity and without diminishing any of PackBagBuddy’s rights to enforce these Terms, PackBagBuddy may cancel such offending Member’s PackBagBuddy Account, permanently block such Member from access to the Service, and take any legal action PackBagBuddy deems appropriate against such Member, including by prosecuting such Member to the fullest extent of the law); impersonate any person or entity, or falsify or otherwise misrepresent yourself or your affiliation or non-affiliation with any person or entity, or otherwise post any reviews that exhibit a conflict of interest (for example, by posting reviews for your or your employer’s Listing); use automated scripts to collect information or otherwise interact with the Services; use the Services to find an Operator or Traveller and then complete a booking of an Group Tour transaction independent of the Services, whether or not you do so in order to circumvent the obligation to pay any Service Fees related to PackBagBuddy’s provision of the Services; as an Operator, submit any Listing with a false or misleading price information, or submit any Listing with a price that you do not intend to honor; post, upload, publish, submit or transmit any Content that:infringes, misappropriates or violates a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy;violates, or encourages any conduct that would violate, any applicable law or regulation or would give rise to civil liability;is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive;is defamatory, obscene, pornographic, vulgar or offensive;promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group;is violent or threatening or promotes violence or actions that are threatening to any other person; or (vii) promotes illegal or harmful activities or substances; systematically retrieve data or other content from the Services to create or compile, directly or indirectly, in single or multiple downloads, a collection, compilation, database, directory or the like, whether by manual methods, through the use of bots, crawlers, or spiders, or otherwise; use, display, mirror or frame any portion of the Services, or any individual element within the Services, PackBagBuddy’s name, any PackBagBuddy trademark, logo or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page, without PackBagBuddy’s express written consent; access, tamper with, or use non-public areas of the Services, PackBagBuddy’s computer systems, or the technical delivery systems of PackBagBuddy’s providers; attempt to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of any PackBagBuddy system or network or breach any security or authentication measures; avoid, bypass, remove, deactivate, impair, descramble, or otherwise circumvent any technological measure implemented by PackBagBuddy or any of PackBagBuddy’s providers or any other third party (including another user) to protect the Services or Collective Content; forge any TCP/IP packet header or any part of the header information in any email or newsgroup posting, or in any way use the Services or Collective Content to send altered, deceptive or false source-identifying information; attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer any of the software used to provide the Services or Collective Content; or advocate, encourage, or assist any third party in doing any of the foregoing.
\n
        </string>
    <string name="tnc4">
<b>Privacy</b>
        \n
See PackBagBuddy’s Privacy Policy and for information and notices concerning PackBagBuddy’s collection and use of your personal information.
\n \n
<b>Ownership</b>
        \n
The Services (including the Site and Application) and Collective Content are protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of Austria and foreign countries. You acknowledge and agree that the Services (including the Site and Application) and Collective Content, including all associated intellectual property rights is the exclusive property of PackBagBuddy and its licensors. You will not remove, alter or obscure any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the Services (including the Site and Application) or Collective Content.
\n \n
<b>PackBagBuddy Content and Member Content License</b>
        \n
Subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions of these Terms, PackBagBuddy grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to (i) access and view any PackBagBuddy Content solely for your personal and non-commercial purposes and (ii) access and view any Member Content to which you are permitted access, solely for your personal and non-commercial purposes. You have no right to sublicense the license rights granted in this section.You will not use, copy, adapt, modify, prepare derivative works based upon, distribute, license, sell, transfer, publicly display, publicly perform, transmit, broadcast or otherwise exploit the Services or Collective Content, except as expressly permitted in these Terms. No licenses or rights are granted to you by implication or otherwise under any intellectual property rights owned or controlled by PackBagBuddy or its licensors, except for the licenses and rights expressly granted in these Terms.
\n \n
<b>Member Content</b>
        \n
We may, in our sole discretion, permit Members to post, upload, publish, submit or transmit Member Content. By making available any Member Content on or through the Services, you hereby grant to PackBagBuddy a worldwide, irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, royalty-free license, with the right to sublicense, to use, view, copy, adapt, modify, distribute, license, sell, transfer, publicly display, publicly perform, transmit, stream, broadcast, access, view, and otherwise exploit such Member Content on, through, or by means of the Services. PackBagBuddy does not claim any ownership rights in any such Member Content and nothing in these Terms will be deemed to restrict any rights that you may have to use and exploit any such Member Content. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for all Member Content that you make available through the Services. Accordingly, you represent and warrant that: (i) you either are the sole and exclusive owner of all Member Content that you make available through the Services or you have all rights, licenses, consents and releases that are necessary to grant to PackBagBuddy the rights in such Member Content, as contemplated under these Terms; and (ii) neither the Member Content nor your posting, uploading, publication, submission or transmittal of the Member Content or PackBagBuddy’s use of the Member Content (or any portion thereof) on, through or by means of the the Services will infringe, misappropriate or violate a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other proprietary or intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy, or result in the violation of any applicable law or regulation. You must not store illegal content on the Site and we will monitor our site regularly for such illegal content. Please be aware that if you upload illegal content you could be subject to a fine of up to INR 100,000.
\n \n
<b>PackBagBuddy Promo Codes or Coupons</b>
        \n
PackBagBuddy may offer Promo Codes or Coupons from time to time providing credits for bookings made on packbagbuddy.com and unless otherwise stated they have an expiry period of 30 days and are limited to one Promo Code per booking. Promo Codes can only be used for bookings for tours and the same basis as outlined in the section: Only one Promo Code can be added/used per booking and they may be combined with Referral Credits.
\n
        </string>
    <string name="tnc5">
<b>Links</b>
        \n
The Services may contain links to third-party websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that PackBagBuddy is not responsible or liable for:the availability or accuracy of such websites or resources; orthe content, products, or services on or available from such websites or resources. Links to such websites or resources do not imply any endorsement by PackBagBuddy of such websites or resources or the content, products, or services available from such websites or resources. You acknowledge sole responsibility for and assume all risk arising from your use of any such websites or resources or the Content, products or services on or available from such websites or resources.
\n \n
<b>Proprietary Rights Notices</b>
        \n
All trademarks, service marks, logos, trade names and any other proprietary designations of PackBagBuddy used herein are trademarks or registered trademarks of PackBagBuddy. Any other trademarks, service marks, logos, trade names and any other proprietary designations are the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective parties.
\n \n
<b>Feedback</b>
        \n
We welcome and encourage you to provide feedback, comments and suggestions for improvements to the Services (“Feedback”). You may submit Feedback by emailing us at contact@packbagbuddy.comYou acknowledge and agree that all Feedback will be the sole and exclusive property of PackBagBuddy and you hereby irrevocably assign to PackBagBuddy and agree to irrevocably assign to PackBagBuddy all of your right, title, and interest in and to all Feedback, including without limitation all worldwide patent, copyright, trade secret, moral and other proprietary or intellectual property rights therein. At PackBagBuddy’s request and expense, you will execute documents and take such further acts as PackBagBuddy may reasonably request to assist PackBagBuddy to acquire, perfect, and maintain its intellectual property rights and other legal protections for the Feedback.
\n \n
<b>Copyright Policy</b>
        \n
PackBagBuddy respects copyright law and expects its users to do the same. It is PackBagBuddy’s policy to terminate in appropriate circumstances the PackBagBuddy Accounts of Members or other account holders who repeatedly infringe or are believed to be repeatedly infringing the rights of copyright holders. If you believe that your property has been used in any way that would be considered copyright infringement or a violation of your intellectual property rights, our copyright agent may be contacted. For more details please click here.
\n
<b>Disclaimers</b>
        \n
IF YOU CHOOSE TO USE THE SERVICES, YOU DO SO AT YOUR SOLE RISK. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT PackBagBuddy DOES NOT HAVE AN OBLIGATION TO CONDUCT BACKGROUND CHECKS ON ANY MEMBER, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, TRAVELLERS AND OPERATORS, BUT MAY CONDUCT SUCH BACKGROUND CHECKS IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. THE SERVICES (INCLUDING THE SITE AND APPLICATION) AND COLLECTIVE CONTENT ARE PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, PackBagBuddy EXPLICITLY DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, QUIET ENJOYMENT OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND ANY WARRANTIES ARISING OUT OF COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE.
\n \n
PackBagBuddy MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT THE SERVICES OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE LISTINGS OR ANY GROUP TOURS WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS. PackBagBuddy MAKES NO WARRANTY REGARDING THE QUALITY OF ANY LISTINGS, GROUP TOURS, THE SERVICES OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT OR THE ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, TRUTHFULNESS, COMPLETENESS OR RELIABILITY OF ANY COLLECTIVE CONTENT OBTAINED THROUGH THE SERVICES. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED FROM PackBagBuddy OR THROUGH THE SITE, APPLICATION, SERVICES OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT, WILL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY MADE HEREIN. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL OF YOUR COMMUNICATIONS AND INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICES AND WITH OTHER PERSONS WITH WHOM YOU COMMUNICATE OR INTERACT AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY OPERATORS OR TRAVELLERS. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT PackBagBuddy DOES NOT MAKE ANY ATTEMPT TO VERIFY THE STATEMENTS OF USERS OF THE SERVICES OR TO REVIEW OR VISIT ANY GROUP TOURS. PackBagBuddy MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE CONDUCT OF USERS OF THE SERVICES OR THEIR COMPATIBILITY WITH ANY CURRENT OR FUTURE USERS OF THE SERVICES.
\n \n
YOU AGREE TO TAKE REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS IN ALL COMMUNICATIONS AND INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICES AND WITH OTHER PERSONS WITH WHOM YOU COMMUNICATE OR INTERACT AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, TRAVELLERS AND OPERATORS, PARTICULARLY IF YOU DECIDE TO MEET OFFLINE OR IN PERSON REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH MEETINGS ARE ORGANIZED BY PackBagBuddy OR TAKE PLACE DURING AN GROUP TOUR. NOTWITHSTANDING PackBagBuddy’s APPOINTMENT AS THE LIMITED AGENT OF THE OPERATORS FOR THE PURPOSE OF ACCEPTING PAYMENTS FROM TRAVELLERS ON BEHALF OF THE OPERATORS, PackBagBuddy EXPLICITLY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR ANY ACT OR OMISSION OF ANY TRAVELER OR OTHER THIRD PARTY.
\n
        </string>
    <string name="tnc6">
<b>Limitation of Liability</b>
        \n
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SERVICES AND COLLECTIVE CONTENT, YOUR LISTING OR BOOKING OF ANY GROUP TOURS VIA THE SERVICES, AND ANY CONTACT YOU HAVE WITH OTHER USERS WHETHER IN PERSON OR ONLINE REMAINS WITH YOU. NEITHER PackBagBuddy NOR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, OR DELIVERING THE SERVICES OR THE COLLECTIVE CONTENT WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA OR LOSS OF GOODWILL, SERVICE INTERRUPTION, COMPUTER DAMAGE OR SYSTEM FAILURE OR THE COST OF SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, OR FOR ANY DAMAGES FOR PERSONAL OR BODILY INJURY OR EMOTIONAL DISTRESS ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS, FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICES OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT, FROM ANY COMMUNICATIONS, INTERACTIONS OR MEETINGS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICES OR OTHER PERSONS WITH WHOM YOU COMMUNICATE OR INTERACT AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES OR FROM YOUR LISTING OR BOOKING OF ANY GROUP TOUR VIA THE SERVICES, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), PRODUCT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT PackBagBuddy HAS BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE, EVEN IF A LIMITED REMEDY SET FORTH HEREIN IS FOUND TO HAVE FAILED OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
\n \n
IN NO EVENT WILL PackBagBuddy’S AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS AND YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, FROM YOUR LISTING OR BOOKING OF ANY GROUP TOUR VIA THE SERVICES, OR FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICES OR COLLECTIVE CONTENT AND IN CONNECTION WITH ANY OR INTERACTIONS WITH ANY OTHER MEMBERS, EXCEED THE AMOUNTS YOU HAVE PAID OR OWE FOR BOOKINGS VIA THE SERVICES AS A TRAVELER IN THE TWELVE (12) MONTH PERIOD PRIOR TO THE EVENT GIVING RISE TO THE LIABILITY, OR IF YOU ARE A GUIDE, THE AMOUNTS PAID BY PackBagBuddyTO YOU IN THE TWELVE (12) MONTH PERIOD PRIOR TO THE EVENT GIVING RISE TO THE LIABILITY, OR ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($100), IF NO SUCH PAYMENTS HAVE BEEN MADE, AS APPLICABLE. THE LIMITATIONS OF DAMAGES SET FORTH ABOVE ARE FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENTS OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN PackBagBuddy AND YOU. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
\n \n
<b>Indemnification and Release</b>
        \n
You agree to release, defend, indemnify, and hold PackBagBuddy and its affiliates and subsidiaries, and their officers, directors, employees and agents, harmless from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, losses, and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, arising out of or in any way connected withyour access to or use of the Site, Application, Services, or Collective Content or your violation of these Terms;your Member Content; andyourinteraction with any Member,booking of an Group Tour,creation of a Listing orthe use, condition or quality of an Group Tour, including, but not limited to any injuries, losses, or damages (compensatory, direct, incidental, consequential or otherwise) of any kind arising in connection with or as a result of participating in or booking a Tour.
\n \n
<b>Export Control and Restricted Countries</b>
        \n
You may not use, export, re-export, import, or transfer the Application except as authorized by Indian law, the laws of the jurisdiction in which you obtained the Application, and any other applicable laws. In particular, but without limitation, the Application may not be exported or re-exported: (a) into any Indian embargoed countries.
\n \n
<b>Reporting Misconduct</b>
        \n
If you participate in an Tour with an Operator who you feel is acting or has acted inappropriately, including but not limited to, anyone whoengages in offensive, violent or sexually inappropriate behaviour,you suspect of stealing from you, orengages in any other disturbing conduct, you should immediately report such person to the appropriate authorities and then to PackBagBuddy by contacting us with your police station and report number at support@packbagbuddy.com provided that your report will not obligate us to take any action beyond that required by law (if any) or cause us to incur any liability to you.
\n \n
<b>Entire Agreement</b>
        \n
These Terms constitute the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between PackBagBuddy and you regarding the Services and Collective Content, and any bookings or Listings of Tours made via the Services, and these Terms supersede and replace any and all prior oral or written understandings or agreements between PackBagBuddy and you regarding bookings or listings of Tours, the Services and the Collective Content.
\n
        </string>
    <string name="tnc7">
<b>Assignment</b>
        \n
You may not assign or transfer these Terms, by operation of law or otherwise, without PackBagBuddy’s prior written consent. Any attempt by you to assign or transfer these Terms, without such consent, will be null and of no effect. PackBagBuddy may assign or transfer these Terms, at its sole discretion, without restriction. Subject to the foregoing, these Terms will bind and inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assigns.
\n \n
<b>Notices</b>
        \n
Any notices or other communications permitted or required hereunder, including those regarding modifications to these Terms, will be in writing and given by PackBagBuddy via email (in each case to the address that you provide) orby posting to the Site or via the Application. For notices made by e-mail, the date of receipt will be deemed the date on which such notice is transmitted.
\n \n
<b>Controlling Law and Jurisdiction</b>
        \n
These Terms will be interpreted in accordance with the laws of Ahmedabad, Gujarat Jurisdiction, without regard to its conflict-of-law provisions. You and we agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of a state court located in Ahmedabad, Gujarat for any actions for which the parties retain the right to seek injunctive or other equitable relief in a court of competent jurisdiction to prevent the actual or threatened infringement, misappropriation or violation of a party’s copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents, or other intellectual property rights, as set forth in the Dispute Resolution provision below.
\n \n
<b>General</b>
        \n
The failure of PackBagBuddy to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not constitute a waiver of future enforcement of that right or provision. The waiver of any such right or provision will be effective only if in writing and signed by a duly authorized representative of PackBagBuddy. Except as expressly set forth in these Terms, the exercise by either party of any of its remedies under these Terms will be without prejudice to its other remedies under these Terms or otherwise. If for any reason an arbitrator or a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Terms invalid or unenforceable, that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible and the other provisions of these Terms will remain in full force and effect.
\n \n
<b>Newsletters</b>
        \n
By registering; using our Services and/or providing your email address, you understand that you will receive regular email updates about the platform, travel and other community related matters. Each email you receive shall contain a mandatory opt out at the base of each email to allow you to unsubscribe if you so choose.
\n \n
<b>Contacting PackBagBuddy</b>
        \n
If you have any questions about these Terms or any App Store Sourced Application, please contact PackBagBuddy at contact@packbagbuddy.com
\n

    </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>


    <string name="report">Report a Problem</string>
    <string name="url">Page URL/link</string>
    <string name="prob">Explain the problem</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="search_elements">Search elements</string>
    <string name="policies">Policies</string>
    <string name="legal_policies">Legal Policies</string>
</resources>